♪I'd rather soar like a mayfly in another dimension♪
♪ أفضل التحليق مثل ذبابة مايو في بعد آخر
♪Restart my life and gaze at the rainbow together♪
♪ أعد تشغيل حياتي وحدق في قوس قزح معًا
♪I do not regret my promise to you♪
♪ لست نادمًا على وعدي لك
=My Deepest Dream=
= أعمق حلمي =
(We lend our helping hands)
(نحن نقدم يد العون)
(to those in need.)
(للمحتاجين).
Sleep properly.
النوم بشكل صحيح.
(Sometimes, we help the weak.)
(في بعض الأحيان ، نساعد الضعفاء).
(Sometimes, it's a small favor.)
(في بعض الأحيان ، تكون خدمة صغيرة).
(Sometimes, we act bravely for the sake of justice.)
(أحيانًا نتصرف بشجاعة من أجل العدالة).
(And sometimes, we give help to those who don't need help,)
(وأحيانًا ، نقدم المساعدة لأولئك الذين لا يحتاجون إلى المساعدة ،)
(still, they're grateful for it.)
(لا يزالون ممتنين لذلك).
=Episode 19=
= الحلقة 19 =
Ye Xunyi, Liu Xiaojiang,
يي شونيي ، ليو شياو جيانغ ،
and Chen Ningmeng were killed by the same person.
و Chen Ningmeng قتلا على يد نفس الشخص.
Besides, tomorrow night,
الى جانب ذلك ، ليلة الغد ،
the culprit will continue his murder.
الجاني سيستمر قتله.
I need your help.
انا بحاجة الى مساعدتكم.
Please tell me the details.
من فضلك قل لي التفاصيل.
Wu Yu, Tan Jiao.
وو يو ، تان جياو.
The specifics of the murderer and the prediction you gave
تفاصيل القاتل والتنبؤ الذي قدمته
are precise.
دقيقة.
But, if you don't have the proof,
لكن ، إذا لم يكن لديك الدليل ،
it can't explain
لا يمكن أن تشرح
how you foresee the future event.
كيف تتوقع الحدث المستقبلي.
I fear I can't help you out.
أخشى أنني لا أستطيع مساعدتك.
Shen Shiyan.
شين شيان.
I understand you can't accept
أنا أفهم أنك لا تستطيع القبول
everything you have heard.
كل ما سمعته.
But, they are all truths.
لكنها كلها حقائق.
Please believe in us.
الرجاء الإيمان بنا.
I can explain this to you later.
يمكنني أن أشرح لك هذا لاحقًا.
There's no need.
ليس هناك حاجة.
All I need is evidence.
كل ما احتاجه هو دليل.
So that I can be responsible for all the victims.
حتى أكون مسؤولاً عن جميع الضحايا.
Shen Shiyan.
شين شيان.
I'd bet my life on them.
أراهن بحياتي عليهم.
Please trust them, alright?
الرجاء الوثوق بهم ، حسنا؟
I'm a cop
أنا شرطي
and I can't let my emotion
ولا أستطيع ترك مشاعري
cloud my judgement.
سحابة حكمي.
What is wrong with you?
ما بكم؟
I'm leaving now.
انا راحل الان.
Yu.
يو.
I'll go and check her out.
سأذهب وأتفقدها.
Zhuang Yu. Yu.
Zhuang Yu. Yu.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
I'm so pissed off.
انا غاضب جدا.
He's just staid
إنه رزين للتو
and rigid.
وجامدة.
Shen Shiyan has his own reason.
شين شيان له سبب خاص به.
I understand.
أفهم.
After all, he's a cop.
بعد كل شيء ، هو شرطي.
If he believes in us blindly,
إذا كان يؤمن بنا بشكل أعمى ،
he'll be
وقال انه سوف يكون
an unqualified cop then.
ثم شرطي غير مؤهل.
Anyway, I don't wish you would have a bad impression of him
على أي حال ، لا أتمنى أن يكون لديك انطباع سيء عنه
because of this.
و لهذا.
Officer Shen.
الضابط شين.
I guess you're curious
أعتقد أنك فضولي
of why we could foresee
لماذا يمكن أن نتوقع
the murderer's plan
خطة القاتل
as well as
إلى جانب
the encounter between you and Zhou Xiaoyu.
المواجهة بينك وبين Zhou Xiaoyu.
It's simple.
انه سهل.
Because we came from the future.
لأننا أتينا من المستقبل.
I watched this game before.
لقد شاهدت هذه اللعبة من قبل.
The final result is four to one.
النتيجة النهائية هي أربعة إلى واحد.
The reason why we came to you
سبب جئنا اليك
is because you were on our side
هو لأنك كنت إلى جانبنا
in three time-travelings before.
في ثلاث رحلات عبر الزمن من قبل.
Three time-travelings?
ثلاث رحلات عبر الزمن؟
Yes.
نعم.
The time Tan Jiao and I experienced keeps moving backwards.
الوقت الذي عشناه أنا وتان جياو يستمر في التحرك إلى الوراء.
We met both of you every time.
التقينا كلاكما في كل مرة.
This is the fourth time we meet.
هذه هي المرة الرابعة التي نلتقي فيها.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
So,
لذا،
you still can't believe us, can you?
ما زلت لا تصدقنا ، أليس كذلك؟
Wu Yu, do you know?
وو يو ، هل تعلم؟
Everything you said
كل ما قلته
is beyond belief.
لا يمكن تصديقه.
To you,
لك،
all these things have yet to happen.
كل هذه الأشياء لم تحدث بعد.
But to me,
ولكن بالنسبة لي،
they were all the history in my memory.
كانوا كل التاريخ في ذاكرتي.
After the murderer kills tomorrow night,
بعد أن قتل القاتل ليلة الغد
his next target
هدفه التالي
is my sister.
هي اختي.
Wu Yu.
وو يو.
I've talked to Zhuang Yu.
لقد تحدثت إلى Zhuang Yu.
She's going with us today.
هي ذاهبة معنا اليوم.
We'll definitely catch that bad guy.
سنمسك بالتأكيد هذا الرجل السيئ.
Although I can't fight
على الرغم من أنني لا أستطيع القتال
like Shen Shiyan does,
مثلما يفعل شين شيان ،
I can take photos of the incident.
يمكنني التقاط صور للحادث.
I'll record the proof.
سوف أسجل الدليل.
No need.
لا حاجة.
I've thought it over.
لقد فكرت في الأمر أكثر.
Zhuang Yu and you must stay at home today.
Zhuang Yu وأنت يجب أن تبقى في المنزل اليوم.
Why?
لماذا ا؟
The enemy we're facing is unlike the previous one.
العدو الذي نواجهه يختلف عن العدو السابق.
I can't put both of you in danger.
لا يمكنني أن أعرض كلاكما للخطر.
What if something bad happens to you?
ماذا لو حدث لك شيء سيء؟
If I don't call you by 2:30 a.m.,
إذا لم أتصل بك بحلول الساعة 2:30 صباحًا ،
call the police.
اتصل بالشرطة.
No way.
مستحيل.
You can't go there alone.
لا يمكنك الذهاب إلى هناك بمفردك.
This is too dangerous.
هذا خطير جدا.
Wu Yu.
وو يو.
Zhuang Yu and I will go with you,
Zhuang Yu وأنا سنذهب معك ،
please.
رجاء.
Eat breakfast.
تناول الإفطار.
Look, who's here?
انظر من هنا؟
Shen Shiyan.
شين شيان.
Yesterday,
في الامس،
I checked with my colleague who's in charge of the case
راجعت مع زميلي المسؤول عن القضية
after I went back.
بعد أن عدت.
The information you provided is real,
المعلومات التي قدمتها حقيقية ،
including that football game.
بما في ذلك لعبة كرة القدم.
That means
هذا يعني
you trust us now, right?
أنت تثق بنا الآن ، صحيح؟
Although, I still can't come around
على الرغم من أنني ما زلت لا أستطيع الحضور
to the fact that you're from the future,
لحقيقة أنك من المستقبل ،
this incident
هذا الحادث
is likely to harm
من المرجح أن يضر
the safety of the people.
سلامة الناس.
If you're right
إن كنت على صواب
about the murder case,
حول قضية القتل ،
I must capture the culprit.
يجب أن ألقي القبض على الجاني.
But, I'm doing this personally.
لكني أفعل هذا شخصيًا.
I'll go with you tonight.
سأذهب معك الليلة.
I know I'm right about you.
أنا أعلم أنني على حق فيك.
Hey.
يا.
But, on one condition,
لكن بشرط واحد
you must report everything to the police
يجب عليك إبلاغ الشرطة بكل شيء
after this.
بعد هذا.
Of course.
بالطبع.
Since you promised to help us,
منذ أن وعدت بمساعدتنا ،
you must spare no effort
يجب ألا تدخر جهدا
to investigate that jerk.
للتحقيق في هذا الأحمق.
Do you hear me?
هل تسمعني؟
Oh?
أوه؟
Staid.
رزين.
Officer Shen.
الضابط شين.
Let's go through the information.
دعنا نذهب من خلال المعلومات.
This is the murder scene
هذا مشهد القتل
and Xu Jingmiao's workplace.
ومكان عمل Xu Jingmiao.
(Music Bar)
(شريط الموسيقى)
If you're really from the future,
إذا كنت حقًا من المستقبل ،
you must know more
يجب أن تعرف المزيد
about this case than me though.
حول هذه الحالة مني رغم ذلك.
Everything I knew
كل ما عرفته
is from the police document,
من وثيقة الشرطة ،
which was told by Ding
الذي رواه دينغ
after my sister was murdered.
بعد مقتل أختي.
Tan Jiao and you have travelled across time
تان جياو وأنت سافرت عبر الزمن
several times.
عدة مرات.
Didn't you find any new threads?
ألم تجد أي مواضيع جديدة؟
The murderer is cunning.
القاتل ماكر.
So, this time
إذن ، هذه المرة
is our best chance to capture him.
هي أفضل فرصة لدينا للقبض عليه.
We were close to the thread
كنا قريبين من الخيط
in every time travel,
في كل وقت سفر ،
however, they're a bit different somehow.
ومع ذلك ، فهي مختلفة بعض الشيء بطريقة ما.
Therefore, I can't be sure
لذلك ، لا يمكنني التأكد
about the murderer now.
عن القاتل الآن.
There must be an unnoticeable breakthrough.
يجب أن يكون هناك اختراق غير ملحوظ.
I still have a question.
لا يزال لدي سؤال.
Tan Jiao and you have travelled across time several times,
تان جياو وقد سافرتم عبر الزمن عدة مرات ،
is there anything that didn't change
هل هناك أي شيء لم يتغير
in the previous universes?
في الأكوان السابقة؟
The thing
الشيء
that never changes
لا يتغير ابدا
is only you and Zhuang Yu.
هو أنت و Zhuang Yu فقط.
Both of us?
كلانا؟
Yes.
نعم.
Regardless of the changes and dangers we've encountered,
بغض النظر عن التغييرات والمخاطر التي واجهناها ،
Zhuang Yu and you would show up.
سوف تظهر Zhuang Yu وأنت.
Strangely.
بغرابة.
Every time we met you,
في كل مرة نلتقي بك
something bad happened.
شيء ما سيء حدث.
I wonder if bad luck falls on us
أتساءل عما إذا كان الحظ السيئ يقع علينا
or you.
او انت.
Honestly, we're lucky.
بصراحة ، نحن محظوظون.
Even if
حتى لو
you were in danger every time
كنت في خطر في كل مرة
or you found what we told you unacceptable,
أو وجدت أن ما قلناه لك غير مقبول ،
your decision never changed.
قرارك لم يتغير.
Just like now.
تماما مثل الآن.
Then,
ثم،
in every universe,
في كل الكون ،
Zhou Xiaoyu and I...
تشو شياويو وأنا ...
You are always together.
أنت دائما معا.
To be frank,
لأكون صريحا،
I have no idea
ليس لدي أي فكرة
why I would believe in your saying
لماذا أؤمن بقولك
about time travel and superpower.
عن السفر عبر الزمن والقوة العظمى.
Aren't these things
أليست هذه الأشياء
only found in novels?
وجدت فقط في الروايات؟
Do you think
هل تعتقد
they'll get angry?
سوف يغضبون؟
Of course, they will.
بالطبع سيفعلون.
Staid Shen
ستيد شين
will surely drive us back,
سيعيدنا بالتأكيد ،
saying that it's dangerous.
قائلا أنه أمر خطير.
Wu Yu will definitely say...
سيقول وو يو بالتأكيد ...
No.
رقم.
He'll...
جحيم...
- Where are they?
- أين هم؟  - أين هم؟
No idea.
لا أعلم.
What are you doing here?
ما الذي تفعله هنا؟
We want to help you.
نريد مساعدتك.
Just take us as your assistants.
فقط خذنا كمساعدين لك.
Right?
حق؟
It's dangerous being here.
من الخطر التواجد هنا.
That's why
لهذا
I'm worried about you.
انا قلق عليك.
Plus, we've overcome so many difficulties together
بالإضافة إلى ذلك ، تغلبنا على العديد من الصعوبات معًا
previously, haven't we?
سابقا أليس كذلك؟
Camera showed that
أظهرت الكاميرا ذلك
Xu Jingmiao was last seen
شوهد شو جينغمياو آخر مرة
at 2:20 a.m.
الساعة 2:20 صباحا
I think that guy will be around here.
أعتقد أن هذا الرجل سيكون هنا.
She's walking in our direction.
إنها تمشي في اتجاهنا.
Don't go home. Someone is tailing you.
لا تذهب للمنزل.  شخص ما يلاحقك.
Run now.
اركض الآن.
Tan Jiao.
تان جياو.
Stay in the car with Zhuang Yu.
ابق في السيارة مع Zhuang Yu.
Call the police.
اتصل بالشرطة.
Okay.
تمام.
I go around from the back.
أتجول من الخلف.
You follow behind her.
أنت تتبعها.
Okay.
تمام.
Stop it!
توقف عن ذلك!
Stand right there.
قف هناك.
Wake up.
استيقظ.
Where's the person?
اين الشخص؟
I lost him.
انا خسرته.
He ran away.
هرب.
What about Xu Jingmiao?
ماذا عن Xu Jingmiao؟
She was sent to the hospital.
تم إرسالها إلى المستشفى.
What has happened?
ماذا حدث؟
We received a report that someone intended to kidnap.
تلقينا بلاغًا يفيد بأن شخصًا ما كان ينوي الاختطاف.
I'm Shen Shiyan, from the Municipal Criminal Police Force.
أنا شين شيان من شرطة الجنايات البلدية.
Request police in this area
طلب الشرطة في هذا المجال
to search around the district.
للبحث في جميع أنحاء المنطقة.
The suspect is around here.
المشتبه به هنا.
He's dangerous.
إنه خطير.
He wears a bucket hat, medium height
يرتدي قبعة دلو متوسطة الارتفاع
and with a knife.
وبسكين.
When did you know Chen Xingjian?
متى عرفت تشين شينغ جيان؟
I'm not close to him.
أنا لست قريبًا منه.
It's been a long time since I last talked to him.
لقد مر وقت طويل منذ آخر مرة تحدثت معه.
When was the last time you saw him?
متى كانت آخر مرة رأيته؟
Two weeks ago, I think.
قبل أسبوعين ، على ما أعتقد.
He was a lounge singer in the bar.
كان مغني صالة في الحانة.
Chen Ningmeng,
تشين نينجمينج ،
Liu Xiaojiang, and Ye Xunyi.
ليو شياوجيانغ ويي شونيي.
Do you know these names?
هل تعرف هذه الأسماء؟
I've never heard of them before.
لم اسمع بهم من قبل.
I don't know them.
لا اعرفهم.
Well, Miss Xu.
حسنا يا آنسة شو.
I hope that you can try to recall it.
آمل أن تتمكن من محاولة تذكرها.
- Please. I want to go home, please. - Shen.
- لو سمحت.  أريد العودة إلى المنزل من فضلك.  - شين.
We've found Chen Xingjian.
وجدنا Chen Xingjian.
You've been working all night. Go back and rest.
كنت تعمل طوال الليل.  العودة والراحة.
I'll handle the rest.
سأتعامل مع الباقي.
How's it now?
كيف الحال الان؟
It's fine.
لا بأس.
Anyway, the culprit is found.
على أي حال ، تم العثور على الجاني.
Everything will be clear.
كل شيء سيكون واضحا.
Are you hungry?
هل انت جوعان؟
I've bought you supper.
لقد اشتريت لك العشاء.
Eat it while it's hot.
تناولها وهي ساخنة.
Excuse me.
اعذرني.
Two beers, please.
جعتان من فضلك.
- Thank you. - Give me a moment.
- شكرًا لك.  - أعطني لحظة.
The scene in which Chen Xingjian was captured
المشهد الذي تم فيه القبض على Chen Xingjian
differs from what you described.
يختلف عما وصفته.
Just minor details, anyway.
فقط تفاصيل ثانوية ، على أي حال.
Probably some minor specifics
ربما بعض التفاصيل الثانوية
were changed in the end
تم تغييرها في النهاية
after we told
بعد أن قلنا
Shen Shiyan.
شين شيان.
Hope so.
امل ذلك.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Come on.
هيا.
Let's celebrate
دعونا نحتفل
that Chen Xingjian is finally captured
أن Chen Xingjian تم القبض عليه أخيرًا
and
و
Miao is safe now.
مياو في أمان الآن.
You must be tired.
يجب أن تكون متعبا.
Rest early.
استرح مبكرا.
Erm...
ERM ...
Thank you for your supper.
شكرا لك على العشاء.
Take a good rest.
خذ قسطا جيدا من الراحة.
I'm closing the door.
أنا أغلق الباب.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
Bye-bye.
مع السلامة.
Wait.
انتظر.
Yes? Anything?
نعم؟  اى شى؟
I'm thirsty.
عطشان.
Can I have some water?
هل أستطيع الحصول على بعض الماء؟
You're thirsty?
انت عطشان؟
Come on in.
تفضل بالدخول.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Please sit.
اجلس لطفا.
I'll get you some water.
سأحضر لك بعض الماء.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
Go, Zhou Xiaoyu.
اذهب ، تشو شياويو.
Don't be scared.
لا تخف.
The great scene in your love life is coming.
المشهد العظيم في حياتك العاطفية قادم.
Come on.
هيا.
Please drink some water.
من فضلك اشرب بعض الماء.
Sure, thank you.
طبعا شكرا لك.
So, you're really thirsty.
لذا ، أنت عطشان حقًا.
It's late now.
فوات الآن.
Rest early.
استرح مبكرا.
Remember to lock your door.
تذكر أن تغلق بابك.
So, he came in just for the water?
إذن ، لقد جاء فقط من أجل الماء؟
Sorry?
آسف؟
Nothing.
لا شئ.
It's my fault.
هذا خطأي.
How would a staid guy flirt?
كيف يمكن لرجل رزين أن يغازل؟
You must be worn out, right?
يجب أن تكون منهكًا ، أليس كذلك؟
We'll discuss it later. About you and me.
سنناقشه لاحقا.  حول لي ولكم.
You can go back and take good rest.
يمكنك العودة والحصول على قسط جيد من الراحة.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
About you and me?
حول لي ولكم؟
Nothing.
لا شئ.
Tan Jiao is coming back soon.
تان جياو سيعود قريبا.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Zhou Xiaoyu.
تشو شياويو.
I know you might find it absurd,
أعلم أنك قد تجده سخيفًا ،
but I think I've fallen for you.
لكني أعتقد أنني وقعت في حبك.
I've never had this strong feeling before.
لم يكن لدي هذا الشعور القوي من قبل.
I feel like I've fallen for you many times
أشعر وكأنني وقعت في حبك مرات عديدة
when I first saw you.
عندما رأيتك لأول مرة.
That's because
هذا بسبب
we've been in love many times.
كنا في حالة حب عدة مرات.
Really?
هل حقا؟
Yes.
نعم.
What are you waiting for?
ماذا تنتظر؟
Oh my...
يا إلهي ...
♪Escapes me♪
يهرب مني ♪
♪No matter♪
♪ لا يهم
♪Which universe you're in♪
♪ في أي عالم أنت فيه ♪
♪Or the wheel of time turns, I'll find you♪
♪ أو تدور عجلة الزمن ، سأجدك ♪
♪The dark cloud and the bright moon are destined to meet♪
السحابة المظلمة والقمر الساطع يتقابلان ♪
We're home.
نحن في المنزل.
Walk slowly.
امشي ببطء.
Careful.
حذر.
Master Qizhu.
سيد Qizhu.
I need your help.
انا بحاجة الى مساعدتكم.
Help me out.
ساعدني.
Miao.
مياو.
Be careful.
كن حذرا.
What happened to him?
ماذا حدث له؟
He's hammered.
لقد ضرب.
He never drinks this much before.
لم يشرب هذا كثيرا من قبل.
He's happy today.
إنه سعيد اليوم.
So, he drank a lot.
لذلك ، شرب كثيرا.
Did you two patch up?
هل قمت باثنين من التصحيح؟
Why are you with him at this late hour?
لماذا أنت معه في هذه الساعة المتأخرة؟
Careful.
حذر.
Did you really patch up?
هل حقا تصحيح؟
Come in.
ادخل.
Hold onto him.
تمسك به.
Careful.
حذر.
Hold onto him, Miao.
تمسك به ، مياو.
Sit.
يجلس.
Did you stay at home
هل بقيت في المنزل
without going anywhere tonight?
دون الذهاب إلى أي مكان الليلة؟
Of course.
بالطبع.
Wu Yu didn't allow me to hang out.
لم تسمح لي وو يو بالتسكع.
He forced me to fold origami stars.
أجبرني على طي نجوم الأوريغامي.
Zhu Yutong and I both have sore hands.
تشو يوتونغ وأنا على حد سواء مؤلمة في اليدين.
Miao.
مياو.
You must take care
يجب أن تعتني
and don't simply go out by yourself.
ولا تخرج بمفردك.
Wu Yu cares about you very much.
وو يو تهتم بك كثيرا.
I know.
أنا أعرف.
But, sometimes he's too strict with me
لكن في بعض الأحيان يكون صارمًا جدًا معي
like I'm a three-year-old child.
كأنني طفل في الثالثة من العمر.
Where's Tan Jiao?
أين تان جياو؟
Jiao.
جياو.
I won't interrupt you then.
لن أقاطعك بعد ذلك.
I'm going to bed now.
انا ذاهب الى السرير الآن.
Goodnight.
تصبح على خير.
Bye-bye.
مع السلامة.
Please continue.
يرجى مواصلة.
♪The changing of weather, the cycle of season♪
♪ تغير الطقس دورة الموسم ♪
♪A cumulonimbus passes by♪
♪ الركام يمر من قبل ♪
♪Meeting you♪
♪ مقابلتك ♪
Rest early.
استرح مبكرا.
Goodnight.
تصبح على خير.
♪Let the story characters♪
♪ دع شخصيات القصة ♪
Tan Jiao.
تان جياو.
You...
أنت...
You need to rest now.
أنت بحاجة إلى الراحة الآن.
Wu Yu.
وو يو.
You!
أنت!
♪Find you♪
♪ تجدك ♪
♪Rain overcoming the clouds♪
♪ مطر يتغلب على الغيوم ♪
♪Through the world and through the wind and rain♪
عبر العالم وعبر الريح والمطر
♪Overcoming adversities is easy, overcoming oneself is hard♪
التغلب على المحن أمر سهل ، والتغلب على الذات صعب ♪
♪Rain overcoming the clouds♪
♪ مطر يتغلب على الغيوم ♪
♪Overcoming the crowd and the future♪
التغلب على الحشد والمستقبل ♪
♪Overcoming myself is easy but overcoming you is hard♪
التغلب على نفسي سهل لكن التغلب عليك صعب ♪
♪The changing of weather, the cycle of season♪
♪ تغير الطقس دورة الموسم ♪
♪A cumulonimbus passes by♪
♪ الركام يمر من قبل ♪
♪Meeting you♪
♪ مقابلتك ♪
♪Like reading the wrong chapter in a serialized novel♪
مثل قراءة الفصل الخطأ في رواية متسلسلة ♪
♪Let the story characters♪
♪ دع شخصيات القصة ♪
♪Never give up no matter how tough it is♪
لا تستسلم أبدًا مهما كانت صعبة ♪
♪Following you♪
♪ متابعينك ♪
Yu.
يو.
Yu?
يو؟
Are you at home?
هل أنت في المنزل؟
Good morning, dear.
صباح الخير عزيزي.
Good morning.
صباح الخير.
You went out so early to buy breakfast.
لقد خرجت مبكرًا لشراء وجبة الإفطار.
Yu.
يو.
I'm wrong.
انا مخطئ.
No.
رقم.
I'm to be blamed.
يجب أن ألوم.
It's my fault.
هذا خطأي.
I should've texted you
كان يجب أن أرسل لك رسالة نصية
or you'd be worried about me.
أو ستقلق عليّ.
Of course, I was going to text you.
بالطبع ، كنت سأرسل لك رسالة نصية.
But, I fell asleep yesterday.
لكني نمت أمس.
Hold on.
يتمسك.
Last night...
ليلة أمس...
Don't take me wrong.
لا تسيء فهمي.
Nothing has happened between us.
لم يحدث شيء بيننا.
Nothing at all.
لاشىء على الاطلاق.
So, you didn't come back last night.
لذا ، لم تعد الليلة الماضية.
Zhou Xiaoyu.
تشو شياويو.
Did you and Staid Shen...
هل أنت و Staid Shen ...
No.
رقم.
Don't overthink.
لا تفرط في التفكير.
Nothing has happened.
لم يحدث شيء.
It's not what you think.
ليست كما تعتقد.
You drive me crazy.
انت تقودني الى الجنون.
Yesterday,
في الامس،
I was waiting for you the whole night.
كنت في انتظارك طوال الليل.
I was so anxious
كنت قلقة جدا
that something might happen to you.
أن شيئًا ما قد يحدث لك.
Good for you.
جيدة بالنسبة لك.
You were staying with Shen Shiyan,
كنت تقيم مع شين شيان ،
enjoying your sweet time together.
الاستمتاع بوقتك الجميل معًا.
You have left me behind.
لقد تركتني ورائي.
It's not what you think.
ليست كما تعتقد.
Nothing happened between us.
لم يحدث شيء بيننا.
I accompanied him to work late into the night.
رافقته للعمل حتى وقت متأخر من الليل.
Massage my legs.
تدليك ساقي.
Well.
نحن سوف.
Tell me.
أخبرني.
How are you going to compensate me?
كيف ستعوضني؟
I'll treat you to a feast.
سأعطيك وليمة.
No.
رقم.
Lipstick?
أحمر الشفاه؟
Let's go shopping.
لنذهب للتسوق.
I'll buy anything you like.
سأشتري أي شيء تريده.
Is that okay?
هل هذا مقبول؟
Deal.
صفقة.
Hold on.
يتمسك.
I left in a rush
غادرت في عجلة من أمري
and threw my clothes onto the bed.
ورمت ملابسي على السرير.
Supposedly,
يفترض ،
if you stayed here last night,
إذا بقيت هنا الليلة الماضية ،
my clothes wouldn't be here.
ملابسي لن تكون هنا.
I was cleaning up just now
كنت أقوم بالتنظيف الآن
and I left it there.
وتركتها هناك.
After I observed you closely,
بعد أن راقبتك عن كثب ،
the clothes you're wearing are the same as yesterday's ones.
الملابس التي ترتديها هي نفسها ملابس الأمس.
Plus, the water heater isn't plugged in
بالإضافة إلى ذلك ، لم يتم توصيل سخان المياه
and the floor is dry.
والأرضية جافة.
Tan Jiao.
تان جياو.
You didn't come back home yesterday.
لم تعد إلى المنزل أمس.
Am I right?
هل انا على حق؟
No.
رقم.
I won't answer you.
لن أرد عليك.
No?
رقم؟
Don't come near, Zhuang Yu.
لا تقترب ، Zhuang Yu.
- You... - No.
- انت، لا.
You lied to me.
لقد كذبت علي
Dear.
عزيزي.
Tell me more
اخبرني المزيد
about my story with Staid Shen.
عن قصتي مع Staid Shen.
Didn't I tell you?
الم اقل لك
You've been together for three lives.
لقد كنتم معًا لمدة ثلاثة أرواح.
I'm curious about
أشعر بالفضول حيال ذلك
the details of the three different lives.
تفاصيل ثلاث حيوات مختلفة.
You said
أنت قلت
I bumped into his car previously.
لقد اصطدمت بسيارته من قبل.
What happened then?
ماذا حدث بعد ذلك؟
Greedy girl.
فتاة جشعة.
Is a sweet not enough for you?
هل الحلو لا يكفي لك؟
Yet you ask for more.
ومع ذلك ، فأنت تطلب المزيد.
I'm planning
انا اخطط
a grand date for him.
موعد كبير بالنسبة له.
I'm sure he never sees
أنا متأكد من أنه لا يرى أبدًا
something like this in his life.
شيء من هذا القبيل في حياته.
I want to scare him.
أريد إخافته.
Scare him?
تخيفه؟
I don't think so.
أنا لا أعتقد ذلك.
You want to overwhelm him with sweetness, don't you?
تريد أن تغمره بالحلاوة ، أليس كذلك؟
Nonsense.
كلام فارغ.
Stop making fun of me.
توقف عن الاستهزاء بي.
How dare you?
كيف تجرؤ؟
Are you going to fill his heart with your love?
هل ستملأ قلبه بحبك؟
Zhuang Yu, you're so sweet.
Zhuang Yu ، أنت لطيف للغاية.
(Criminal Investigation Unit of Kaifu Branch, Jinghai Public Security Bureau)
(وحدة التحقيق الجنائي بفرع كايفو ، مكتب جينغهاي للأمن العام)
He confessed.
اعترف.
Really?
هل حقا؟
Great.
رائعة.
But, he confessed sexual harassment allegation.
لكنه اعترف بمزاعم التحرش الجنسي.
He said he had a crush on Xu Jingmiao for a long time.
قال إنه كان معجبا بـ Xu Jingmiao لفترة طويلة.
Yesterday, he's beside himself and he harassed her.
بالأمس ، كان بجانب نفسه وضايقها.
He was crying over his action last night.
كان يبكي بسبب عمله الليلة الماضية.
He hopes Xu Jingmiao will forgive him.
إنه يأمل أن يغفر له Xu Jingmiao.
But, the priority now is
لكن الأولوية الآن
that we can't prove
لا يمكننا إثباته
he's the murderer of the serial killings.
إنه قاتل عمليات القتل المتسلسلة.
What about his alibi?
ماذا عن عذره؟
Does he have that?
هل لديه ذلك؟
We've already known
لقد عرفنا بالفعل
the time of the three murder cases.
وقت جرائم القتل الثلاث.
However, no one noticed if he went out.
ومع ذلك ، لم يلاحظ أحد ما إذا كان قد خرج.
Therefore,
وبالتالي،
no alibi.
لا عذر.
What's the conclusion then?
ما هي النتيجة إذن؟
We have to release him
علينا إطلاق سراحه
if we have no proof.
إذا لم يكن لدينا دليل.
He's the murderer.
إنه القاتل.
You can't release him.
لا يمكنك إطلاق سراحه.
You were with me that night...
كنت معي في تلك الليلة ...
Wu Yu!
وو يو!
What's your proof?
ما هو دليلك؟
If no,
إذا كان الجواب لا ،
how do you prove he's the murderer?
كيف تثبت انه القاتل؟
I...
أنا...
We've thoroughly searched Chen Xingjian's place,
لقد بحثنا بدقة في مكان Chen Xingjian ،
the bar where he used to sing,
الحانة حيث اعتاد الغناء ،
his studio
مرسمه
and his car,
وسيارته ،
but nothing has been found.
لكن لم يتم العثور على شيء.
There's no sign of him committing a crime at all.
ليس هناك ما يشير إلى أنه ارتكب جريمة على الإطلاق.
Wu Yu.
وو يو.
To be on the safe side,
لتكون في الجانب الآمن ،
Captain Ding and I will keep a close eye
أنا والكابتن دينغ سنراقب عن كثب
on him.
عليه.
But for now,
لكن الان،
we have to release him.
علينا إطلاق سراحه.
Shen.
شين.
After Chen Xingjian is released,
بعد إطلاق سراح Chen Xingjian ،
Huang and you
هوانغ وأنت
will supervise him all day long.
سيشرف عليه طوال اليوم.
Never let your guard down.
لا تدع الحرس الخاص بك إلى أسفل.
Yes.
نعم.
Wu Yu.
وو يو.
Thank you for cooperating with us throughout the investigation.
شكرا لتعاونك معنا طوال التحقيق.
We're good citizens.
نحن مواطنون صالحون.
It's our duty
إنه واجبنا
to cooperate with the police.
للتعاون مع الشرطة.
But, I hope
ولكن أتمنى
there'll be no such absurdity happening to us again.
لن يكون هناك مثل هذا السخف يحدث لنا مرة أخرى.
If you're the murderer,
إذا كنت القاتل ،
I won't spare you.
لن أنقذك.
It's fine.
لا بأس.
I accept your apology.
انا قبلت عذرك.
This is your girlfriend, right?
هذه صديقتك ، صحيح؟
She's so beautiful.
انها جميلة جدا.
Do keep a close eye on her.
راقبها عن كثب.
Say that again.
قل ذلك مرة أخرى.
Wu Yu.
وو يو.
Nine days more
تسعة أيام أخرى
before you leave this timeline.
قبل أن تغادر هذا الجدول الزمني.
We'll supervise him all day long
سنشرف عليه طوال اليوم
to make sure that he won't harm anyone.
للتأكد من أنه لن يؤذي أحداً.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
Tan Jiao.
تان جياو.
Move all your things out of Zhuang Yu's house.
انقل كل أغراضك من منزل Zhuang Yu.
From now on,
من الان فصاعدا،
you'll stay at my house.
ستبقى في منزلي.
Why, Wu Yu?
لماذا ، وو يو؟
Didn't you hear him?
ألم تسمعه؟
History changed
تغير التاريخ
since the moment we caught him.
منذ اللحظة التي أمسكنا بها.
I have no idea
ليس لدي أي فكرة
about his plan in the future.
عن خطته في المستقبل.
No need to change your shoes.
لا حاجة لتغيير حذائك.
Master Qizhu.
سيد Qizhu.
Welcome to our house.
مرحبا بك في منزلنا.
I've prepared
لقد أعددت
the slippers, toothbrush, and towel.
النعال وفرشاة الأسنان والمنشفة.
I wonder tonight...
أتساءل الليلة ...
- We sleep together. - We sleep in separate rooms.
- ننام معا.  - ننام في غرف منفصلة.
It seems you have different opinions.
يبدو أن لديك آراء مختلفة.
You may take some time to discuss this.
قد تأخذ بعض الوقت لمناقشة هذا.
Wu Yu.
وو يو.
Let's dine out tonight
دعونا نتناول العشاء في الخارج الليلة
to celebrate
من اجل الاحتفال
that you've patched up with Master Qizhu.
التي قمت بتصحيحها مع Master Qizhu.
Didn't I tell you
ألم أخبرك
that the murderer
أن القاتل
is likely
ومن المرجح
to harm Tan Jiao again?
لإيذاء تان جياو مرة أخرى؟
So, the two of you
لذا ، أنتما الاثنان
must stay at home.
يجب أن تبقى في المنزل.
Do you hear me?
هل تسمعني؟
I have to attend classes though.
لا بد لي من حضور الدروس بالرغم من ذلك.
I'll ask for a leave on your behalf.
سأطلب إجازة نيابة عنك.
Why do you drag me in?
لماذا تسحبني إلى الداخل؟
Listen to him.
استمع اليه.
Well, Miao.
حسنا مياو.
You have to understand
يجب ان تفهم
that Wu Yu is protecting you.
أن وو يو يحميك.
Crap.
حماقة.
I know he cares about me.
أعلم أنه يهتم بي.
But, I'm bored.
ولكني أشعر بالملل.
Also, I have a business on campus to deal with.
أيضا ، لدي عمل في الحرم الجامعي للتعامل معه.
Well,
نحن سوف،
perhaps you put it aside first.
ربما وضعتها جانبا أولا.
After all, your safety matters the most.
بعد كل شيء ، سلامتك هي الأهم.
Listen to your brother.
استمع لأخيك.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
I miss you too.
أفتقدك أيضًا.
Tan Jiao.
تان جياو.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Do you need my help?
هل تحتاج مساعدتي؟
No need.
لا حاجة.
I just want to make sure you're fine.
أريد فقط أن أتأكد من أنك بخير.
Never leave my sight,
لا تترك بصري ابدا
okay?
حسنا؟
Look.
نظرة.
When you are busy,
عندما تكون مشغولا
I'm out of your sight.
أنا بعيد عن نظرك.
Sounds reasonable.
يبدو معقولا.
Aren't you
لا انت
being too exaggerated?
أن تكون مبالغا فيه؟
It's impossible that Chen Xingjian has a superpower
من المستحيل أن يكون لدى Chen Xingjian قوة عظمى
and suddenly turns up here
وفجأة يظهر هنا
to catch me.
للقبض علي.
Well done.
أحسنت.
Keep on talking.
الحفاظ على الحديث.
Are you going to stay outside the bathroom
هل ستبقى خارج الحمام
when I take a shower?
عندما أستحم؟
What did you say? Louder, please.
ماذا قلت؟  بصوت أعلى من فضلك.
Nothing.
لا شئ.
I said
انا قلت
you're such a discreet
أنت متحفظ للغاية
and resourceful high achiever.
وإنجازات عالية الحيلة.
Speaking of this,
بالحديث عن هذا ،
you haven't gone to the campus for a long time.
لم تذهب إلى الحرم الجامعي لفترة طويلة.
How could you finish your paper?
كيف يمكنك إنهاء ورقتك؟
I've finished it already.
لقد انتهيت من ذلك بالفعل.
Waiting for the graduation ceremony.
في انتظار حفل التخرج.
What's your plan
ما هي خطتك
after graduation?
بعد التخرج؟
Do you want to stay in Jinghai
هل تريد البقاء في جينغهاي
or Da...
أو دا ...
What happened?
ماذا حدث؟
Are you alright? Get up.
هل انت بخير؟  استيقظ.
I...
أنا...
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
I just fell.
لقد وقعت للتو.
You scared me.
لقد أخفتني.
We'll discuss the plan together
سنناقش الخطة معًا
after my graduation, right?
بعد تخرجي صحيح؟
I'm sorry to interrupt you.
أنا آسف لمقاطعتك.
Wu Miao.
وو مياو.
I sleep in the living room.
أنام ​​في غرفة المعيشة.
Call me if you need help.
اتصل بي إذا كنت بحاجة للمساعدة.
If I snore loudly,
إذا شخرت بصوت عالٍ ،
you can wake me up.
يمكنك إيقاظي.
No, you won't.
لا ، لن تفعل.
You're quiet when you sleep.
أنت هادئ عندما تنام.
Am I?
هل انا
♪May time flies♪
♪ قد يطير الوقت
♪May you appear before me♪
♪ قد تظهر أمامي ♪
♪May you hold my hands♪
♪ أرجو أن تمسك يدي ♪
♪As you take the oath♪
كما تحلف اليمين
♪May you live a thousand years♪
♪ أتمنى أن تعيش ألف سنة ♪
♪May you live a life full of love♪
♪ عسى أن تعيش حياة مليئة بالحب
♪May your heart skip a beat♪
♪ قد يتخطى قلبك الخفقان ♪
♪Whenever you meet me♪
متى تقابلني ♪
♪May you have a space♪
♪ قد يكون لديك مساحة
♪To watch my previous love life♪
♪ لمشاهدة حياتي العاطفية السابقة ♪
♪May you have clairvoyance♪
♪ قد يكون لديك استبصار ♪
♪To see when we will meet♪
لنرى متى سنلتقي
♪The fish and the bird♪
السمكة والعصفور
♪Who is meeting whom♪
♪ من يلتقي بمن ♪
♪How deep does our love go and whose life will be spent?♪
ما مدى عمق حبنا ومن ستمضي حياته؟
♪The cloud and the moon♪
♪ السحابة والقمر ♪
♪Who runs into whom?♪
♪ من يصطدم بمن؟
♪Flowers bloom and wilt as time passes by♪
تتفتح الأزهار وتذبل بمرور الوقت ♪
♪May you live a thousand years♪
♪ أتمنى أن تعيش ألف سنة ♪
♪May you live a life full of love♪
♪ عسى أن تعيش حياة مليئة بالحب
♪May your heart skip a beat♪
♪ قد يتخطى قلبك الخفقان ♪
♪Whenever you meet me♪
متى تقابلني ♪
♪May you travel far and wide♪
قد تسافر بعيدًا وواسعًا ♪
♪To witness all flavors of love♪
لتشهد كل نكهات الحب ♪
♪May you travel with me♪
♪ قد تسافر معي ♪
♪For the blissful moments to come♪
للحظات الهناء القادمة ♪
♪The cloud and the moon♪
♪ السحابة والقمر ♪
♪Who is meeting whom♪
♪ من يلتقي بمن ♪
♪How deep does our love go and whose life will be spent?♪
ما مدى عمق حبنا ومن ستمضي حياته؟
♪The fish and the bird♪
السمكة والعصفور
♪Who runs into whom?♪
♪ من يصطدم بمن؟
♪Flowers bloom and wilt as time passes by♪
تتفتح الأزهار وتذبل بمرور الوقت ♪
♪The cloud and the moon♪
♪ السحابة والقمر ♪
♪Whose and whose oath is it?♪
لمن هذا اليمين؟
♪How deep does our love go and whose attachment is this?♪
ما مدى عمق حبنا ومن هذا الارتباط؟
♪The fish and the bird♪
السمكة والعصفور
♪Whose and whose trial of love is this?♪
لمن هذه ومحبة من هذه؟
♪Flowers bloom and wilt as we shine in time♪
تتفتح الأزهار وتذبل مع تألقنا بمرور الوقت ♪